## Juan David Lizarralde Niño

Full Stack Developer

React Js | Node Js | Express Js | Mongo DB | AWS | GitHub | Salesforce | WordPress

Visual & Multimedia professional.

Four years of experience in Multimedia Marketing. With more than two years of experience in Web Development. I worked in a company and now as a freelance. My dream is to help with my knowledge, and my energy. I want to grow up in my career and resolve problems in the development world

Bogotá, Colombia
(57) 310 755 9990
juand.lizarralden@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/juandal
nino
https://github.com/JUANDAL

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Freelance** — Full Stack Developer

DEC 2021 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with the team to design, structure, and implement new websites from start to finish.
- Updated existing websites
- Developed a user-friendly architecture, and provided support and customer services.
- Developer & Support for companies and projects. Working with WordPress, and Elementor for designs. WooCommercer for sales & I'm worked with SalesForce for CRM.

### **TEDI**, Colombia — Web Developer

JAN 2020 - JUN 2022

- Design and develop the official web page for TEDI (2020)
- Modified HTML, JS, and CSS web pages to optimize the page's performance for faster loading and browsing
- E-mail developer, responsible for developing email, using HTML, CSS, and media queries.
- Utilized strategic engineering procedures to maintain and improve the company's web application
- Working with Salesforce CRM & Cloud. Development in the platform for solutions

### **EDUCATION**

# **Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano**, Colombia — Bachelor of Film and MultiMedia

IAN 2014 - DEC 2018

**IBM** — DevOps, Cloud, and Agile Foundations Specialization

MAR 2022 - JUL 2022

### ${\bf freeCodeCamp-Legacy\,Full\,Stack\,Certification}$

DEC 2021 - DEC 2023

### **SKILLS**

NINO

- Cloud Computing
- Web Application &Development
- Database & Servers
- Proficient Troubleshooting
- Technical Process Improvement
- Leadership

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

DevOps, Cloud, and Agile Foundations | IBM 2022

Responsive Web Design | freeCodeCamp 2022

JavaScript Developer | CoderHouse 2022

### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish native English professional (B2)